let prog_question = [
    {
        question:"Type of Low Level Computer Programming Language that Simplifies the Language of Machine Code.",
        choices:{
            a:"Python Language",
            b:"Javascirpt",
            c:"Assembly Language"
        },
        answer:'Assembly Language'
    },
    {
        question:"A Computer Programming Language Created by John Backus for Complicated Scientific, Mathematical, and Statistical Work this programming language stands for Formula Translation",
        choices:{
            a:"C Language",
            b:"Fortran",
            c:"Java"
        },
        answer:'Fortran'
    },
    {
        question:"Developed by Dennis Ritchie, and considered by many to be the first high-level Computer Porgramming Language, and influenced many other languages including C#, Ruby, Go, Java, PHP, ang Python. ",
        choices:{
            a:"C Language",
            b:"COBOL",
            c:"PASCAL"
        },
        answer:'C Language'
    },
    {
        question:"Developed by Donald Chamberlin, used for viewing and changing information that is stored in database and stands for Structure Query Language.",
        choices:{
            a:"SQL",
            b:"MATLAB",
            c:"C++"
        },
        answer:'SQL'
    },
    {
        question:"Developed by Microsoft, allows programmers to choose and change pre-selected chunks of code in a drag-and-drop fashion through a Graphical Useer Inteerface (GUI).",
        choices:{
            a:"MATLAB",
            b:"R Language",
            c:"Visual Basic"
        },
        answer:'Visual Basic'
    },
    {
        question:"A sub program that takes parameters and RETURNS a value.",
        choices:{
            a:"Function",
            b:"Parameters",
            c:"Syntax"
        },
        answer:'Function'
    },
    {
        question:"Creator of Python.",
        choices:{
            a:"Steve Jobs",
            b:"Guido Van Rossum",
            c:"Rasmus Lerdorf"
        },
        answer:'Guido Van Rossum'
    },
    {
        question:"The arrangement of words and phrases to create well-formed sentences in a language.",
        choices:{
            a:"Format",
            b:"Syntax",
            c:"Comments"
        },
        answer:'Sytnax'
    },
    {
        question:"A set of instructions in the style of a programming language, but using plain English.",
        choices:{
            a:"Code",
            b:"Program",
            c:"Pseudocode"
        },
        answer:'Pseudocode'
    },
    {
        question:"A value that cannot be altered during the running of the program.",
        choices:{
            a:"Constants",
            b:"Program",
            c:"Variables"
        },
        answer:'Constants'
    },
    {
        question:"What is it called when two or more strings are combined to form one big string?",
        choices:{
            a:"Sort",
            b:"Logic",
            c:"Concatenating"
        },
        answer:'Concatenating'
    },
    {
        question:"Classification of Data being stored.",
        choices:{
            a:"Variables",
            b:"Data Type",
            c:"Data"
        },
        answer:'Data Type'
    },
    {
        question:"A location in memory where data is being stored.",
        choices:{
            a:"Variable",
            b:"Data Type",
            c:"Constants"
        },
        answer:'Variable'
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is a programming language that is interpreted.",
        choices:{
            a:"Go",
            b:"Python",
            c:"C++"
        },
        answer:'Python'
    },
    {
        question:"Finite set of steps which, if followed, accomplish a particular task.",
        choices:{
            a:"Algorithm",
            b:"Logic",
            c:"Code"
        },
        answer:'Algorithm'
    },
    {
        question:"A structure which can repeat a set of statements up to a fixed number of times or until a certain criterion is satisfied.",
        choices:{
            a:"Condition",
            b:"Logic",
            c:"Loop"
        },
        answer:'Loop'
    },
    {
        question:"Executable instructions which are operated in the direct mode.",
        choices:{
            a:"Command",
            b:"Execute",
            c:"Opperate"
        },
        answer:'Command'
    },
    {
        question:"Pictorial representation of a program which helps in understanding the flow of control and data in the algorithm.",
        choices:{
            a:"Flowchart",
            b:"Line",
            c:"Opperation"
        },
        answer:'Flowchart'
    },
    {
        question:"Process of finding and removing errors in a program. In this process, the program is thoroughly checked for errors.",
        choices:{
            a:"Debugging",
            b:"Programming",
            c:"Checking"
        },
        answer:'Debugging'
    },
    {
        question:"The process in which a function calls itself directly or indirectly is called ______ and the corresponding function is called as recursive function.",
        choices:{
            a:"Recursion",
            b:"Function Call",
            c:"Loop"
        },
        answer:'Recursion'
    },
  ]